fsoft4down.com 2014-05-20

# Software and Driver Updates - FilesFrog.com

Somoto Ltd. (herein “The provider”) is committed to your privacy. Please read our policies below: 

The provider recognize the need to protect the privacy of the personal information of our users. Users should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the use of that information. 

## No Spyware Policy

The provider never tracks or stores your personal identifiable information. We may send unidentifiable and non-personal data and use it to maintain the correct operation of the web site. The IP address is used to customize your experienced based on your locale, including to correctly assign language presentation. Any information gathered is done on an aggregated basis and in no way can be linked to private information such as private individual name, address, telephone or email, which is never collected or stored. 

## No Adware Policy

The provider does not launch pop-up or pop-under advertisement windows or any other type of obtrusive ads. Users may be presented with advertisements while using roaming the site. We might use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies which may be collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

If you choose to contact us we will ask you for your name and email address. We do not store this information but simply receive it as one time email. You may contact us at http://software.filesfrog.com/general/contact to request that we remove this email from our email inbox. 

## Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our web site if you do so. We use cookies to make it easy to our visitors to download graphics on our site. We also use cookies to collect demographic and profile data on an aggregate basis for purposes of delivering content specific to users interests. 

## IP addresses

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as "traffic data" so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you. We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. The provider will not use your IP address to attempt to identify your personal information. 

## Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## External links and Software

Contains links and downloads of third party software as well as links to third-party Web sites. Please be aware that we cannot control and are not responsible for the information collection practices of third-party software and Web sites. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of these software and Web sites before providing any information to them. 

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or application, or your dealings with them, you can contact us [here](http://software.filesfrog.com/general/contact).
